http://www.raregoldcoins.com/privacy-policy

Concierge Service/
About/About DWNAbout DougWe're BuyingWhat Our Customers SaySales Tax InformationFAQ
Market Blog/
Articles/
Education/Doug's BooksCoinapediaso you want to collectCoin of the Week
Concierge Service/
About/About DWNAbout DougWe're BuyingWhat Our Customers SaySales Tax InformationFAQ
Market Blog/
Articles/
Education/Doug's BooksCoinapediaso you want to collectCoin of the Week
Contact/
Privacy StatementLAST UPDATED: 01/01/2014The following statement has been developed to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy.OverviewRareGoldCoins.com collects personally identifiable information (name, e-mail address, etc.) and/or demographic data (zip code, gender, interests, etc.) that you submit when you: 1) register for our services, 2) complete a survey, 3) register for a promotion, contest, or sweepstakes, 4) make a purchase from our online store, or 5) send us an email. We and/or our 3rd party partners may use this information to process and maintain your account, compile demographic statistics about our users, and display to you information and advertisements that match your interests and profile.Financial information will be provided to third parties only to provide products and services that you order. We may use the contact information you provide to contact you about your account and/or to send you necessary information directly related to the product(s) or service(s) for which you have registered. With your permission, we may use your contact information to inform you of new features and special offers from RareGoldCoins.com. We will not provide your contact information to unaffiliated third parties without your express permission. As part of the registration process, you have the option to inform us that you do not wish to receive information about other special offers and promotions.CopyrightsAll content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, and software, is the property of RareGoldCoins.com or its content suppliers and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. The compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement, and assembly) of all content on this site is the exclusive property of RareGoldCoins.com and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. All software used on this site is the property of RareGoldCoins.com or its software suppliers and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display, or performance, of the content on this site is strictly prohibited.IP Addresses and CookiesRareGoldCoins.com uses IP addresses (random numbers assigned to individual computers) to help diagnose problems with our servers, administer our web site, and anonymously track content preferences and traffic patterns. We also use cookies (small text files transferred from our Web site to your hard drive) to recognize repeat users, track usage behavior, and facilitate your access to and use of our site. Cookies do not damage files or allow anyone to access your personally identifiable information – they simply allow us to tailor information and advertisements to make your visits more enjoyable and meaningful (and enable us to provide you with personalized information, if you choose). They also provide information to us about site usage to help us improve and update our site. We may share aggregate (not individual) site usage statistics and demographic information with advertisers and other third parties, but this information will not include any personally identifiable information.Security and LinksThe security of the information you provide to RareGoldCoins.com is important to us. We use encryption software and other security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of sensitive information under our control. However, the RareGoldCoins.com site includes links to other sites, and when you choose to visit those sites, we are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat user information. In addition, we may permit third parties to offer registration-based services through our site. We are not responsible for the actions and policies of these third parties, and you should review the privacy policies of these parties when supplying personally identifiable information to them.Additional InformationRareGoldCoins.com reserves the right to alter our Privacy Policy as business needs require. Any changes will be posted to our web site in a timely manner. This statement and the policies outlined here are not intended to and do not give you any contractual or other legal rights.
Home/
Inventory/
New Book/
Concierge Service/
About/About DWNAbout DougWe're BuyingWhat Our Customers SaySales Tax InformationFAQ
Market Blog/
Articles/
Education/Doug's BooksCoinapediaso you want to collectCoin of the Week
Contact/
Douglas Winter Numismatics
Search our Blog/Articles
$2.50 - 1860 Clark Gruber PCGS AU58 CAC
10,750.00
$2.50 - 1883 PCGS PR63CAM CAC
10,500.00
$5.00 - 1807 Bust Right NGC MS63
*
Thank you!
PO Box 4383 Portland, OR 97208 | 214.675.9897
Join our Preferred Customer List
Join the DWN Preferred Customer List
Name
*
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
*
How did you find DWN?
*
Google/internet search
Facebook
Instagram
Twitter
Print Advertising
PCGS message boards
other
Thank you!
Privacy PolicyDWN collects all applicable sales taxes from AR, HI, KS, KY, ME, MN, MS, NV, NJ, NM, NY, OH, TN, VT, WV, WI, DC.© Douglas Winter Numismatics 2012-2020 | All Rights Reserved.Photography by Jenna Van Valen. Site design by Sarah Moon.
